Frasier mss., 1934-2014 LMC 2962
Lilly Library
- Suicide in the Entertainment Industry
  - Hyman, Phyllis (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Hyson, Kevin (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Inge, William (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Ingersoll, Fred (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Ingraham, Arthur P. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Irene (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Irene - photograph of death site (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Israel, Richard (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Itami, Juzo (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Jackson, Charles (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Jackson, Glenn E. (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Jacobs, David (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Jacobson, Tom (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Jammer, Cal (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Janes, Luther C. (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Jarnegin, Jerry (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Jarnegin, Jerry - crime scene photograph (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Jason, Rick (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Jelin, Max J. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Jenkins, J. Elliott (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Jenkins, Jimmy (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Jerome, Suzie (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Johannesson, Cary Jon (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Jones, Audrey (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Jones, Keith (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Jones, Rita (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Jordan, Alex (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Jorden, Albert Paul (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Journee, Jeannette (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Judd, Terence (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Judels, Jules (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Julien, Pauline (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Jullion, M. Arthur (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Justice, Barry (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Jutra, Claude (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Kaimann, William (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Kaliski, Louis (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Kappel, Adolph (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Kastel, Philip (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Kauter, William (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Kearney, Patrick (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Keats, Steven (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Keenan, Geraldine (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Keim, Adrienne La Champ (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Keith, Brian (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Keith, Brian - photograph of headstone (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Kellin, Nina C. (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Kelly, Anthony Paul (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Kennedy, Kevin J. (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Kennedy, Pat (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Kenney, C. E. (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Kent, Kay (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Kibbee, Donald Guy (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - King, Allyn (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - King, Edward L. (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - King, Edwin (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Keegan, Terry (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Kinney, Anthony (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Klaw, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Klugherz, John A. (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Koenig, Frank (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Korsten, G. E. (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Kortum, Lawrence (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Krause, Ben (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - La Franie, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Ladd, Alan (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Ladd, Alan - photograph (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Lafferty, Jeannette (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Lagrange, Vivian (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Lake, Alan (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Lamont, Owen (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Lamy, Newland (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Lancer, Martin (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Landis, Carole (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Landis, Carole - photograph (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Larkin, William (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Lasalle, Bob (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Lashley, H. T. (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Lassen, Elna (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Lazarus, Isaac (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Laszlo, Lola (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Laughlin, Leo C. (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Lavrova, Vera (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Lawrence, Eddy (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Lawrence, Florence (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Lawrence, Florence - photograph (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Lazarus, Sidney (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Lebrun, Jean (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Lee, Harry (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Lee, Tommy (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Lee, W. Albert (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Leeds, Doris Theresa (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Lehman, Trent (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Leigh, Megan (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Lesley, Carole (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Leslie, Lula (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Lessey, May Abbey (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Levine, Hendrick (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Levitt, Robert D. (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Levy, Adolph (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Levy, Raoul (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Lewis, Gordon (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Lewis, Ronald (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Lewis, Thurston T. (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Liddy, Lewis W. (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Linder, Max (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Linder, Max - photograph (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Lindsey, Ouida (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Linkletter, Diane (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Linkletter, Diane - photograph of death site (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Little, Little Jack (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Livingston, Charlotte (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Llewelyn, Jacqueline (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Loeb, Philip (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Long, Ray (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Long Lance (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Lorimer, Wright (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Lothrop, William H. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Love, Robert (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lowers, Helen (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Lubetkin, Steve (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Luciano, Ron (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ludwig, Charles (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Luftig, Charles (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Lygo, Mary (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - McClelland, George F. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - McCoy, Charles "Kid" (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - McCullough, Paul J. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - McCutcheon, Wallace (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - McDermott, Joe
  - McDonald, Sidney T. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - McDowell, James Nelson (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - McElroy, Gavin B. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - McFarland, Homer S. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Mafarlane, Peter Clark (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - McIntire, Donald E. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - MacIsaac, Fred John (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Mack, William (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Mackenzie, Billy (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - McKenna, Kyle (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - McNamara, Maggie (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - McPhail, Allen (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - McPhail, Douglas (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Maeno, Mitsuyasu (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Mahan, Vivian L. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Major, John (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Manker, Roy L. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Mann, Fred (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Manuel, Richard (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Markle, John (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Martin, Vallie Belasco (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Martorana, Samuel (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Marvin, Mark (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Maryott, Susan (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Maskell, Virginia (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Mason, Lew (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Massengale, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Massey, Edward (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Massingham, Dorothy (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Mastrocola, Enrico (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Mathiesson, Fiona (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Matsumoto, Hideto (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Maynard, Claire (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Mayorova, Yelena (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Meins, Gustave (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Meins, Gustave - photograph (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Melrose, Kitty (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Mendelssohn, Eleonora (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Merrige-Abrams, Salwa (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Merrill, Bob (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Messenger, Frank (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Metz, Henry (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Midgley, Rex W. (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Mildwater, Justin (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Miller, Charles B. (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Millington, Mary (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Minch, Conrad H. (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Miroslava (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Mohamed, Hamid Ben (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Moloney, Jay (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Monroe, Marilyn - photograph (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Mont, Helen Kim (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Moora, Robert L. (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Moore, Cecil (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Moore, Lotus (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Moorey, Stefa (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Moorhead, Chester (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Moriarty, Joanne (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Morphy, Lewis H. (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Morris, Chester (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Morris, Chester - photograph (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Morris, Leonard (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Morrison, Fred (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Mossman, James (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Mottley, Eva (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Moult, Ted (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Moyer, Helen (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Muller, Ben (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Mulligan, Griffin (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Munrow, David (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Munson, Ona (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Munson, Ona - photograph (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Murray, Oscar J. (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Murray, Paul (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Nagle, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Neal, Sandra (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Nehoda, Ron (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Nelson, Billy (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Nelson, Evelyn (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Nelson, Evelyn - photograph of death site (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Newey, Murray (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Nirenska, Pola (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Noel, Dawn Hope (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Norden, Cliff (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Obee, Richard Rippon (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - O'Brien, Pat (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Ochs, Phil (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - O'Connor, Hugh (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Odoms, Clifford R. (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - O'Donnell, Helen (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Ogden, William (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - O'Hara, Brian (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Okada, Yukiko (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - O'Keefe, Mildred (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Olmedo, Alberto (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Olsen, John C. (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - O'Neill, Peggy (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - O'Neill, Peggy - photograph of death site (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Oram, Suzanne (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Orbes, Marceline (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Osterman, Mary (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Paine, William O. (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Pascal, Christine (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Patrick, Warren A. (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Patz, Louis (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Pavlevy, Andreas (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Payne, Donald Rollie (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Peck, Jonathan (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Perkins, Frank (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Perry, Geraldine (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Peters, Gleason G. (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Peterson, Frederick (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Phillips, Genevieve (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Phillips, Twila (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Pierce, Jackie (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Pierce, Justin (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Pike, Nita (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Piper, Franco (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Pistilli, Luigi (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Plato, Dana (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Pollack, Ben (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Polyakuu, Eugene (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Pond, Lloyd (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Popescu, Stere (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Powell, Nicolette (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Powell, William Jr. (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Preeman, Mouse M. (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Presburg, Yolanda (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Preston, Walter G. Jr. (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Prevo, Alice Munn (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Prince, Ben S. (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Prinze, Freddie (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Prinze, Freddie - photograph (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Purks, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Putnam, J. Myles (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Quigley, Jay (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Quine, Richard (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Ramos, Flor Morales (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Rand, George (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ransom, Edith (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Rapp, Danny (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Rappaport, David (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Rawlins, Judy (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Ray, Margaret Mary (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Raymond, Leslie Ray (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Redding, Earl (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Rehse, George W. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Rennie, Hugh (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Reynolds, Florence (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Reynolds, Lynn (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Reynolds, Fred (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Richards, Ann (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Richerts, Frederick (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Ritchie, Perry V. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Rivera, Carlos (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Roberts, Albert G. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Roberts, Nellie (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Roberts, Rachel (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Robinson, Madeleine (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Rocamora, Wynn (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Rockwell, George (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Rogers, Gustavus A. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Rogers, Will Jr. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Rose, Joel (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Rose, Monica (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Rosenberg, Edgar (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Ross, Arthur H. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Ross, Robin (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Rosson, Richard (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Rosson, Richard - photograph of death site (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Row, Harry (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Rudolph, Mina (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Sampson, Caleb (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Sanders, George (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Sanders, George - photograph (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Sanders, Steve (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Saper, Marshall (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Saunders, John Monk (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Savannah (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Scala, Gia (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Scala, Gia - photograph (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Scala, Gia - poster for The Two Headed Spy (Ovflat 34)
  - Scarboro, David (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Schoenstadt, Ralph (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Schuetze, Carl (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Schwartz, Adele (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Schloss, Berrick (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Scoggin, Travis M. (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Scott, George (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Scott, George (II) (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Scott, Robert Crozier (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Scott, Russell (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Seberg, Jean (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Selkirk, Andres (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Semenoff, Nikolai (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Serkin, Robert (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Sessions, Lynn (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Shannon, Del (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Sheridan, Philip R. (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Sherrin, Scott (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Sherwood, Robert C. (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Shields, Hugh M. (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Shields, Jimmie (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Sidney, Carrie Webb (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Siegel, Norman (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Simmons, Earl (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Sire, Albert L. (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Skelton, Georgia (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Sklover, Theodora K. (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Skouras, Dionysia (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Slater, Charles Dundas (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Slezak, Walter (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Sloane, Everett (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Smith, Edward J. (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Smith, Pete (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Smith, Worthington D. (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Smitha, Silk (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Smoller, Dorothy (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Snyder, Sadie (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Soriero, Thomas D. (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Southern, Dixie Lee (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Spears, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Spirescu, Oscar (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Spitzer, Henry M. (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Sprinkle, Arthur P. (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Stark, Peter (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Steele, Ernest William (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Steele, Murray (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Stegmeyer, Alan (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Stein, Solomon B. (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Steinburg, Jacob (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Sterling, Charles (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Stevens, Inger (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Stevens, Inger - photograph (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Stewart, Iain (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Stewart, Jay (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Stierheim, Christopher (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Storm, Rory (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Street, Mel (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Strickland, David (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Styles, Patricia (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Sullavan, Margaret (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Sullavan, Margaret - photograph (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Sutch, Lord (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Swift, Charlie (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Taintor, Katherine Grey (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Tandler, Adolph (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Tannehill, Frank A. (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Tasker, Robert Joyce (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Taylor, Donald F. (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Taylor, Gene (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Taylor, Mae Linnie (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Tearle, Malcolm (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Teed, James (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Tellegen, Lou (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Tellegen, Lou - photograph (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Tembo, Biggie (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Tenco, Luigi (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Thlies, Henry R. (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Theobald, Dolly (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Thirkield, Robert Leeming (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Thirsk, Jason (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Thomas, Olive (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Thompson, Carlos (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Thompson, Edith (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Thompson, Hallett (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Thompson, Jack (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Thorne, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Tibbetts, William (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Todd, George M. (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Todd, Seamus (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Todd, Thelma - photograph (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Townsend, William H. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Toye, John (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Traina, Nicholas (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Tucker, E. William (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Tuckner, Howard (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Turner, Irene Laura (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Twelvetrees, Helen (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Twelvetrees, Helen - photograph (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Utrera, Adolf (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Van Cott, J. Marston (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Van Dyke, Nancy (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Van Riper, Kay (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Van Zandt, Philip (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Varnadore, Thurman (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Vega, Carlos (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Velez, Lupe (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Velez, Lupe - photograph (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Vidot, Charlotte (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Villechaize, Herve (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Villasenor, Edgar Ricardo (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Vincent, James (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Visaria, Ravi (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Vogel, Patricia F. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Vogelsang, Roland F. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Vollman, William (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Von Erich, Chris (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Von Erich, Kerry (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Von Erich, Mike (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Von Kreisler, Alexander (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Wade, Richard (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Wagner, George E. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Walcamp, Marie (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Walcamp, Marie - photograph (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Waldman, Josef (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Walker, E. Clarke (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Wallace, Ray Charles (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Walsh, May (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Ward, Jeff (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Warfel, Jack (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Waring, Peter (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Warlock, Peter (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Watson, Marion Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Weaver, Howard E. (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Weaver, Doodles (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Webb, Richard (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Webb, Richard - photograph (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Webster, George Hopkinson (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Wegeforth, Gustavus A. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wehle, Billy (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Weiss, Lewis Allen (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Weiss, Phillip (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Wells, Jake (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Wells, Marie (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - West, Vera (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Westmore, George (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Weston, Charles H. (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Whale, James (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Wickware, Francis Sill (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Wildberg, Constance (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Wilder, Mildred Havican (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Wilkinson, Kevin (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Williams, Paul (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Williams, Rozz (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Williams, Rozz - photo postcard (Box 9, Folder 65)
    Sent by photographer Melinda Lewis to Kenneth Anger
  - Williams, Wendy O. (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Willingham, Harry G. (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Willis, Debbie (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Willis, Lynn A. (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Wilmott, Lee (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Wilson, Al (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Wilson, Jack (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Wilson, Read (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Winchell, Jennie (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Winkler, Alexander (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Winship, Emory (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Winter, Julian (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Wise, Fred (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Wiswell, Louis C. (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Withers, Grant (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Wolf, Jutta (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Wolfenden, Stuart N. (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Woodson, Mary (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Yamamota, Tojo (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - York, Duke (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Young, Faron (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Younger, A. P. (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Zegart, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Zimmerman, Frank G. (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Zinn, A. M. (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Zoltai, Stephen (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Unused entries
    - Armstrong, Edwin H. (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Arnstein, Bobbie (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Barnett, Christopher (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Benderoth, Alexander (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Blackmore, Thomas E. (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Bowen, Frances (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Bruce, Mrs. Al (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Burns, Barbara (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Clairmont, Paul de (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Condello, Mike (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Conley, Mazie (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Cowper, Eleanor Merton (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Denby, Edwin (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - McLeod, Barbara (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Meeker, Richard (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Miersch, Johannes (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Minor, Vivian Baldwin (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Morena, Sena (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Nesbitt, Albert J. (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - North, Robert (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - O'Neill, Eugene Jr. (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Papke, Billy (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Preston, Tara (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Prevost, Marie (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Qing, Jiang (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Ranke, Marie (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Reilly, Frank K. (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Russell, Gail (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Salvason, Sigrum (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Secord, Mrs. George (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Sherwood, Cliff (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Smaney, June (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Steiner, Gary A. (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Sterzinger, Caroline Ann (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Toller, Ernst (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Turney, Douglas (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Upward, Allen (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Viafora, Gianni (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Vicky (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Photocopies - photographs and research material (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Jana Harris - correspondence and photographs (Box 9, Folder 132)
    Harris provided some photographs for the book
  - Notebook (Box 9, Folder 133)
- John Wayne Gacy
  Some appear to be enclosures to correspondence and/or given to Frasier by Gacy
  - Question of Doubt - typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
  - Clippings on exhibitions of Gacy's art, 1988-2011 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "The Thin Blue Line" screenplay by Gacy with clippings, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Clippings about Gacy, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Clippings on exhibitions of Gacy's art, 1988-2011 (Ovflat 34)
  - JacKas collectibles order forms, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Photographs of Gacy (copies), undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Floor-plan drawing of Gacy's home by Gacy, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "Murder is my Beat: Me and Mr. Gacy" by Frasier - draft, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Murder is my Beat" - notebook, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Frasier and Gacy photograph, December 1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Ephemera from Frasier's Gacy visit, 1988-1990? (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Show Business Homicides
  - Abbott, Darrell (Dimebag) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Adamson, Al (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Akeman, David "Stringbean" (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Albrecht, Jeffrey Carter (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Anand, Dinesh (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Arbuckle, Roscoe "Fatty", 2 Folders (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
  - Arbuckle, Roscoe "Fatty" - photograph with signature facsimile (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Arcady, John (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Bachemin, Johnnie (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Bacon, David G. G. (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Baloi, Gito (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Bany, Michael (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Barrett, Carlton (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Barsi, Judith (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Beasts of Satan (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Behrmann, Dimitri (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Bender, Christopher L. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bennison, Louis (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Bennison, Louis - photograph (Box 11, Folder 3)